hear the stories were covering this week
听听这周报道的故事
in the category 5 TV newsrooms BTW is
在BTW的5类电视新闻中心
adding angie junk call filters to their
添加安吉垃圾电话过滤器
phone service an autonomous transit bus
电话服务自动过境巴士
is being tested in Las Vegas salesmen
正在拉斯维加斯 销售人员进行测试
latest laptop is one hundred dollars
最新的笔记本电脑是一百美元
cheaper if you buy it with a boon to
如果你用一个恩惠 来购买便宜的话
yahoo wants to change its name and
雅虎想改变它的名字和
google has revealed how they secured
谷歌已透露他们如何获得保障
their cloud infrastructure and it
他们的云基础设施和它
includes some clever custom-built
包括一些聪明的定制
silicon these stories are coming right
硅这些故事是 正确的
up don't go anywhere Jeff Weston Yellin
最多不要去任何地方， 杰夫·韦斯顿 耶林
you're building a brand new beautiful
你正在构建一个全新的美丽
website what are you alright you're
网站你是什么好吧
terrible actor what does we're acting
可怕的演员，我们在做什么？
comes into play I don't know where
发挥作用我不知道在哪里
Arctic you're supposed to act okay are
北极，你应该采取行动没问题
we building a really cool website are
我们建立了一个 非常酷的网站
you building a really cool website you
你建立一个非常酷的网站你
need hosting one of the things about a
需要托管一个关于a的东西
hosting account is you don't want to
托管帐户是你不想
have limitations put on your website
对您的网站有限制
it's true how much hard drive space you
这是真的，你有 多少硬盘空间
have how many email account how many
有多少电子邮件帐户有多少
domains can point to it well we've got
域可以指向我们已有的
an amazing deal for you for a very
对于你来说，这是一笔惊人的交易
limited time cap five dot TV / dreamhost
限时五顶点电视/ dreamhost
for just five dollars and a bit of
只有五美元和一点点
change per month you are going to get
每个月你 会 得到 更改
unlimited web site hosting unlimited
无限的网站托管无限
email accounts on that hosting service
该托管服务上的电子邮件帐户
you are also going to receive a free
你也会收到免费的
domain name the route put your own com
域名路线把你自己的COM
dice to put that amazing website but
骰子把这个惊人的网站，但
you've been working on on there if you
你一直在那里工作，如果你
run if you want to build a wordpress
运行， 如果你想建立一个wordpress
site fine sign up cat5 TV / dream hope
网站很好地注册cat5 电视/梦想的希望
still compatible papers are just don't
仍然兼容的论文只是不
do it but hey it's a great deal folk
这样做，但嘿，这是一个很大的民间
best deal you're going to find five
最好的交易你会找到五个
dollars and change per month go to cap
美元和每月变化达到上限
five dot TV / dreamhost there we go i'm
五点电视/ dreamhost在那里我们走我
sascha through madison here are the top
通过麦迪逊sascha这里是顶部
series for the week of january 18th 2017
系列为2017年1月18日的一周
behave recorded more than 31 million
表现超过3100万
nuisance calls in a single week before
骚扰电话在一个星期之前
Christmas and is doing something about
圣诞节和正在做一些事情
it the company supplies forty percent of
它公司供应百分之四十
the landlines in the UK BTW is now
现在在英国BTW的座机
launching a new service for its
为其推出新服务
customers which it says could block up
客户说它可能会阻止
to 30 million such a nuisance calls per
到3000万这样的骚扰电话
week called BTW call protects the system
一周称为BTW呼叫保护系统
monitors call data to identify rogue
监视呼叫数据以识别流氓
numbers it will for example highlight
它会例如突出显示的数字
phone numbers that make an unusually
电话号码，使异常
large number of calls those calls will
这些呼叫将会有大量的呼叫
then be automatically diverted into a
然后被自动转移到一个
junk voice mailbox the system will
系统将垃圾语音信箱
continue to block such callers even if
即使如此，仍继续阻止这样的呼叫者
they change their number a common tactic
他们改变他们的数量是一种常见的策略
used by solicitors customers will also
律师客户也会使用
be able to identify nuisance callers
能够识别滋扰呼叫者
that get through by dialing the code
通过拨 码 打通
after receiving such a call talktalk
接到这样的通话后， talktalk
introduces a similar central call
引入了类似的中央呼叫
blocking system for landlines three
地面线路阻断系统三
years ago while vodafone operates a
几年前， 沃达丰经营一家
system for mobiles super cool idea i
系统为手机超酷的想法我
wonder if you can just dial a code after
想知道你是否 可以 在之后拨打代码
somebody called you and you don't want
有人打电话给你 ，你不想要
to talk whenever you are yeah except as
只要你是耶，就会说话
long as it just keep them from calling
只要它不让他们打电话
you again yeah we have this from our
你再一次，我们有这个来自我们的
magicjack where we get constant
魔术师在那里我们不断
solicitors calling and it's a big
律师打电话，这是一个很大的问题
problem and we've got a particular
问题，我们有一个特定的问题
solicitor that calls every single day
每天都会打电话的律师
drives my wife not you know one by name
驱动我的妻子，不知道你的名字
no yeah it's FDR oh yeah so we called
不，是的， 这是FDR噢，所以我们打电话
magic jack and so you used to have this
魔术杰克，所以你曾经有过这个
service to block a particular number do
服务来阻止特定的号码做
you still have that and they said no
你仍然有 ，他们说不
they don't have it anymore so we're
他们没有了，所以我们
looking at you know can i build a device
看着你知道我可以建立一个设备
with raspberry pi right that you know
与你知道的覆盆子pi正确
intercepts the calls that's an adjuster
拦截调节器的调用
them and then rings the in-house line
他们然后敲响内部线路
there might be something on github or
在github上可能会有一些东西
write code there might already out there
写代码可能已经在那里了
oh yeah you can't really really hurt my
哦，你真的不能真的伤害我
work day before because yes if they get
前一天工作，因为如果他们得到的话
our number and they start calling
我们的号码，他们开始打电话
sometimes they'll call it 45 second
有时他们会把它叫做45秒
intervals like they're calling and then
像他们打电话那样的间隔
call it and I works perception it as
称之为，我认为它是
very big big chiropractic clinic I need
我需要的非常大的大型脊骨神经科诊所
the fun you gotta take the call yeah I
你总得乐趣接电话啊， 我
I'm a programmer full time I sit at a
我是一个全职的程序员，我坐在一个
desk and I code and there's nothing like
书桌和我的代码，没有什么
answering the call and it's some
接听电话，这是一些
solicitor
律师
or robot and now I've lost 15 minutes of
或机器人，现在我已经失去了15分钟 的时间
my day in the two seconds that it took
我花了两秒钟的时间
to hang up on them because I've got okay
挂断他们，因为我没事
where the heck was I am my code here I
在哪里， 我是我的代码在这里
got ivory go back over the stuff I was
象牙回到了我的东西上
doing and figure out where I was right
做和找出我是对的
surprise me not so we got to build a
让我感到惊讶，所以我们必须建立一个
system this is going to be an upcoming
系统这将是即将到来的
feature I promise you that raspberry pi
功能，我答应你，树莓派
or some other device where the chest
或胸部的其他设备
filter phone calls by phone number how's
通过电话号码过滤电话号码怎么样
that sound no BP got it going on hmm all
那声音没有得到 BP 它会在 所有 HMM
right a small autonomous bus called an
正确的一辆小型自动公交车叫做
arma is running a short route along Las
阿尔玛沿着拉斯维加斯沿着一条短路线行驶
Vegas's Fremont Street marking according
拉斯维加斯的弗里蒙特街标记根据
to transit operator Keolis the first
以过境运营商Keolis为首
time a self-driving bus has new
时间自驾车的新车
passengers on an American public road
美国公共道路上的乘客
the route is short just three blocks and
路线很短，只有三个街区
this is only a pilot test which started
这只是一个开始的试点测试
a week ago woman will end on friday
一周前女人会在星期五结束
while detects the fully electric box can
同时检测完全电箱盒
carry around a dozen passengers moving
随身携带着十几名乘客
at a top speed of limited to 16 miles
最高时速限制在16英里
per hour though the bus is capable of
尽管巴士有能力，但每小时
hitting 30 miles per hour the bus has
击中30英里每小时的 总线 已
sensors that detect obstacles and an
检测障碍物的传感器
emergency button that any passenger can
紧急按钮，任何乘客都可以
use to stop the vehicle during the test
用于在测试过程中停止车辆
there's also a staffer on board to
船上还有一名职员
monitor passenger safety that's a really
监控乘客的安全，这是一个真正的
great idea navya the french company that
好主意navya法国公司
makes the ARMA has already deployed
使ARMA已经部署
vehicles in Singapore France and
新加坡法国和新加坡的车辆
Australia Nevada has a strategic
澳大利亚内华达州具有战略意义
interest in developing transportation
对交通发展的兴趣
technology the state could benefit from
技术国家可以从中受益
easier or long-distance transportation
更方便或长途运输
to gambling centers from California
到加州的赌博中心
while autonomous vehicles like the mafia
而像黑手党这样的自主车辆
boss could provide flexible
老板可以提供灵活的
transportation for visitors once they
运输为游客一旦他们
make it to Vegas I like this idea I like
使它成为维加斯我喜欢这个想法我喜欢
that it's right but it does remind me of
这是对的，但它确实让我想起了
like just a street elevator and I think
就像街道电梯一样，我想
to myself if anybody could in any way
如果有人能以任何方式对我自己
stop the bus at any time by pressing a
按任意键停止公交
button you don't want like six year olds
按钮，你不想像六岁的孩子
on this bus no they could they would
在这辆公共汽车上，他们可以
just like continue it look at what
只是 想继续它看什么
happens when I start pushing buttons
当我开始按下按钮时会发生
well so he goes well I like turn off
好，所以他很好，我喜欢关掉
your like will ferrell and elf you just
你会喜欢你的小精灵
make it a Christmas tree with the
使它成为一棵圣诞树
elevator right you go in information
电梯 吧，你去信息
every single but yes exactly yeah I'm
每一个，但是，是的， 我是
dealing with that you're dealing yeah
处理你处理耶
yeah we got this yeah really cool it's
是的，我们得到了这个真的很酷
exactly like an elevator on the street
就像街上的电梯一样
an autonomous bus
一辆自动公交车
could be smart could be good I do like
可能会很聪明， 我可以做得很好
that it keeps people who have been
它保留了曾经的人
drinking at the at the casinos off the
在赌场喝酒
streets I'll be a pretty good i draw
街道我会很好画画
obligation to be the actual guy who sits
有义务成为真正的坐着的人
there to stick all day just to tell you
在那里坚持整天只是为了告诉你
ride the bus all day no it's like yeah I
整天坐公共汽车不，它就像是 我一样
like the like the guard on a steam train
就像蒸汽火车上的守卫一样
like yeah no well I mean it makes sense
像是没有好，我的意思 是有道理的
for now especially with the technology
现在尤其是技术
still being new but like we see all
仍然是新的，但像我们看到的一切
these other companies like you said ARMA
像你说的其他公司像ARMA
is unlike France and all these other
不像法国和所有这些其他
countries but we also see other
国家， 但 我们也看到其他
companies like uber who tried their um
像超级公司这样的公司尝试过他们
self-driving it was shut down that's
自动驾驶它被关闭了
right I know forgot i'm still doing it
对我知道忘了 我还在做
in on some parking lot yes i'm not even
在一些停车场是的， 我 甚至 没有
like a sweet-looking bus like that hot
就像一辆酷似巴士的甜美巴士
spring yeah yeah you go ahead that's
春天是啊是的，你继续那是
pretty much right yeah I like it and you
几乎是正确的， 我喜欢它和你
know what its kind of secure in its own
知道它自己的安全性
in the fact that it's so visible it's
事实上它是如此明显
not like people could just be on that
不像人们可能就这样
bus like yeah just doing things I
巴士就像是只是做事情我
shouldn't be doing this you can see you
不应该这样做，你可以看到你
know hands to yourselves people say
知道人们会说自己的手
security on board like a great school
就像一所优秀的学校一样
dance right ok you win in Vegas dell has
跳舞右键确定你在拉斯维加斯赢得了
announced the immediate availability of
宣布立即可用
the dell precision 35 20 laptop and
戴尔Precision 35 20笔记本电脑和
buyers can save over one hundred dollars
买家可以节省一百多美元
by choosing a boon to 16.4 LTS preloaded
通过选择预载 16.4 LTS的恩惠
instead of Windows 10 yay Delbarton
而不是Windows 10 yay Delbarton
George says more of Bluetooth Howard
乔治说更多的蓝牙霍华德
precision work stations will go on sale
精密工作站将开始销售
in the coming months worldwide including
在未来几个月内全球包括
anna bunton of the company's stylish new
anna bunton是该公司时尚新款
precision 5720 all-in-one desktop pc
精密5720一体式台式电脑
unlike other vendors dell doesn't ship
不像其他厂商戴尔不出货
their linux option on no frills reduced
他们的Linux选项没有装饰减少
power hardware all models in the Dell
戴尔所有型号的电源硬件
Precision lineups pack powerful seventh
精准的阵容包装强大的第七
generation Intel Core and intel xeon
新一代英特尔酷睿和英特尔Xeon
processors support us bc thunderbolt 3
处理器支持我们bc thunderbolt 3
and can have up to thirty two gigabytes
最多可以有三十二千兆字节
of ram wow the dell precision 35 20 is
ram哇戴尔精确度35 20是
available now nice that sounds like a
现在可以很好听起来像一个
sweet mobile workstation which is
这是甜蜜的移动工作站
basically a laptop that is built for
基本上是一个笔记本电脑，是专为
business writing a business for the
商务写作 的 一个业务
business money you might get a better
企业资金你可能会变得更好
system get a really sweet system file
系统得到一个非常可爱的系统文件
here's the thing you could save your
这里是你可以保存 你的 事
hundred bucks because you probably
百元，因为你可能
already have a computer that came with
已经有了一台电脑
the windows license even if you wanted
即使你想要 Windows许可证
to put windows on it maybe dual boot or
把窗户上它也许双重引导或
something yes my laptop my desktop they
是的我的笔记本电脑我的桌面他们
all came with a windows license so
所有这些都带有Windows许可证
what's to stop me I'm going to upgrade
什么是阻止我我 要升级
my my laptop let's buy this brilliant
我的 笔记本电脑让我们买这个辉煌的
new dell and take the license off of
新戴尔并取消许可
this one put it on there install and
这一个把它放在那里安装和
KaBlam right now I still got windows and
KaBlam现在我仍然有窗户和
linux dual booting but save 100 bucks at
linux双启动，但节省100美元
the same time though it's really
尽管这是真的
exciting because it's do you think I'm
令人兴奋，因为你认为我是
not saying that mainstream is a good
不是说主流是好的
thing or whatever um but do you think
事情或者其他什么，但你认为呢
it's also going to make more users of
它也将使更多的用户
Linux because it's coming pre-installed
Linux，因为它预装了
right right certainly could people maybe
对的人当然可以
because it's going to normalize that
因为它会规范化
people won't be so scared of Linux I
人们不会如此害怕Linux I
work in a place where some of the people
在一些人的地方工作
I work with are afraid of Linux like
我的工作都害怕Linux
it's only by name yeah not I actually
它只是名义上，而不是我其实
don't actually use it there just cared
不要在那里使用它，只是在乎
to make this way they do use it but they
以这种方式，他们确实使用它，但他们
don't know that they use it and that's
不知道他们使用它，就是这样
the thing a lot of your devices already
东西很多 你的设备 已经
have linux on it and you don't realize
有它的Linux，你不知道
it so then when someone says they will
那么当有人说他们会的时候
sell you a computer with linux on it oh
向你推销一台装有linux的电脑哦
I don't know don't know I don't know how
我不知道我不知道如何
to use that right well technically and
在技术上和技术上使用这个权利
then own a watch my job yes volvo sasha
然后拥有一块手表，我的工作是沃尔沃萨沙
it but technically you could be
它但技术上你可能会
considered an astronaut then because
当时认为是一名宇航员，因为
nasa uses linux now in the space station
美国国家航空航天局现在在空间站使用Linux
right because they scrapped the windows
因为他们报废了窗户
computer yeah i read yeah so technically
计算机是的， 我在 技术上 读取 耶
Sasha you could apply to be an astronaut
萨沙你可以申请成为一名宇航员
because you know how to rekal enix
因为你知道如何rekal enix
computer there you go oh that's all I
电脑在那里你走了，这就是我的全部
keiko real guys no it'll be about we
keiko真正的家伙不，它会关于我们
just offended a lot of astronauts I
刚刚冒犯了很多宇航员
actually could not do it I'm a people
实际上做不到我是一个人
person there's not very many people out
那里的人不是很多
in space okay so that yeah that's just
在太空中好吧，这样就可以了
now Sasha that's about to change space
现在萨沙这是即将 改变空间
tourism yahoo revealed in a filing with
旅游雅虎在备案中透露
the securities and exchange commission
证券交易委员会
that the company would change its name
该公司将改变它的名字
to altova after
之后的 阿尔托瓦
it completes its transformation from an
它完成了它从一个转换
actual business to a corporate wrapper
实际业务到企业包装
around Alibaba stock if all goes was
围绕阿里巴巴的股票，如果一切顺利的 WAS
planned CEO Marissa Mayer would step
计划中的首席执行官玛丽莎迈耶会迈出
down the board would be trimmed and Alta
下来董事会将被修剪和阿尔塔
ba would simply continue to exist as a
巴将继续存在作为一个
way for investors to own a chunk of a
投资者拥有一大块钱的方式
non-controlling interest in a Chinese
非控制性的中国人的利益
e-commerce company whether that
电子商务公司是否如此
transformation happens as the result of
转化发生的结果
a successful sale of the Yahoo internet
雅虎互联网的成功销售
portal to verizon or some other less
门户网站verizon或其他一些较少
desirable outcome has yet to be
理想的结果还没有
determined it still far from a sure bet
确定它还远远没有确定的赌注
that the verizon acquisition will go as
Verizon收购将如期完成
planned the change to alta ba apparently
计划明显向alta ba转变
some non trademark infringing sort of
一些非商标侵权行为
reference to alibaba in which yahoo all
参考其中雅虎所有的阿里巴巴
holds a 15% stake depends on the
持有15％的股份依赖于
completion of the sale to verizon of
完成对Verizon的销售
yahoo holdings the new corporate wrapper
雅虎持有新的企业包装
for its internet business verizon
为其互联网业务verizon
initially offered four point eight
最初提供了四点八
billion dollars to Yahoo for light Yahoo
十亿美元雅虎 雅虎光
last July but the deal was in doubt
去年7月份，交易仍然存在疑问
after it was revealed that yahoo had
在揭示雅虎之后
failed to disclose a huge security
未能透露巨大的安全
breach in 2014 to customers and verizon
2014年向客户和Verizon泄露
a second major breach dating to 2013 was
2013年的第二大漏洞是
discovered later we reported on both you
我们后来发现我们都报道过你
be sure did right yes Verizon's planned
请确定Verizon的计划 是正确 的
for the Yahoo brand isn't completely
对于雅虎品牌并不完全
clear other than it would be somehow
除了它会以某种方式清除
aligned or merged with AOL which verizon
与Verizon的AOL对齐或合并
acquired for 4.4 billion dollars in 2015
2015年收购44亿美元
and is still in the process of
并仍在进行中
assimilating given that Yahoo's
同化雅虎的
management is not in a position to go
管理层无法前进
look for a better offer Yahoo would have
寻找更好的 雅虎会有的 报价
to pay verizon a 145 million dollar
向Verizon支付1.45亿美元
termination fee to walk away from the
终止费从走开
table and find another buyer and there
表，并找到另一个买家
isn't exactly a long line of people
并不是很长的一行人
looking to make a better offer it may
希望能够提供更好的报价
end up having to settle for whatever
最终不得不解决任何问题
Verizon decides as a purchase price at
Verizon决定作为购买价格
this point or wait for verizon to walk
这一点还是等待Verizon走路
away from the deal verizon has already
远离 交易verizon已经
reportedly knocked 1 billion dollars off
据报道敲了10亿美元
of its offer oh
它的报价哦
1 billion dollars Sasha we've talked
我们谈过的萨沙10亿美元
about this before its 1 billion the
关于这之前它的10亿美元
correct correct pronunciation is that 1
正确的发音是1
billion dollars okay dr. evil yeah so I
十亿美元好的 博士。邪恶 是啊，所以我
mean that's just it is what it is when
这意味着它就是这样
you lie about your stuff you get one
你说谎你的东西你得到一个
also have a yahoo account after like all
像所有人之后也有一个雅虎帐户
those hi I'm surprised to find that yeah
那些嗨，我很惊讶地发现是的
I did because I used flicker I wall here
我做到了，因为我在这里用了闪烁灯
thoughts mention that too is that I'm
想法提到，我也是
gonna have a user flicker as well so
也会有用户闪烁
it's like what's going to happen to us
这就像我们将要发生的事情
right so that's that dave has one that's
对，所以这是戴夫有一个
his main email is Yahoo time to move on
他的主要电子邮件是雅虎时间继续前进
yeah I know he was a mail address and
是的，我知道他是一个邮件地址和
this is why the price is going down is
这就是价格下降的原因
because users are saying okay I don't ya
因为用户说好，我不是你
I don't trust this I know anymore even
我不相信我知道甚至
better all night you know for anything
对于任何事情 你都知道更好的夜晚
I'm fine like an email address fine
我很喜欢电子邮件地址
google has published an infrastructure
谷歌已经发布了基础架构
security design overview that explains
安全设计概述说明
how it secures the cloud it uses for its
它如何保护它用于它的云
own operations and for public cloud
自己的操作和公共云
services revealed last Friday the
服务上周五透露的
document outlines six layers of security
文件概述了六层安全
and reveal some interesting factoids
并揭示一些有趣的事实
about the alphabet subsidiaries
关于字母表子公司
operations none more so than the
没有比操作更多的操作
revelation that we also design custom
我们也设计定制的启示
ships including a hardware security chip
船舶包括硬件安全芯片
that is currently being deployed on both
目前正在部署这两者
servers and peripherals these chips
服务器和外设这些芯片
allow us to securely identify and
让我们安全地识别和
authenticate legitimate Google devices
验证合法的Google设备
at the hardware level yeah the silicon
在硬件层面是的硅
works alongside cryptographic signatures
与密码签名一起工作
employed over low level components like
用于像低级别组件一样
the BIOS boot loader kernel and based
BIOS引导加载程序内核和基于
operating system image these signatures
操作系统镜像这些签名
can be validated during each boot or
可以在每次启动或验证期间进行验证
update update the document says adding
更新更新文件说增加
that the components are all Google
这些组件都是Google
controls built and hardened with each
控制内置和硬化与每个
new generation of hardware we strive to
我们努力的新一代硬件
continually improve security for example
例如不断提高安全性
depending on the generation of server
取决于服务器的生成
design we root the trust of the boot
设计我们根植于引导的信任
chain in either a lockable firmware chip
链锁在一个可锁定的固件芯片中
a microcontroller running Google written
一个运行Google的微控制器
security code or the above-mentioned
安全码或上述
Google designed security chip
谷歌设计的安全芯片
the document goes on to explain that
该文件继续解释这一点
Google fleet of applications and
谷歌应用程序和
services encrypts data before it is
服务在数据加密之前对其进行加密
written to disk to make it harder for
写入磁盘以使其更难
malicious disk firmware to access data
恶意磁盘固件来访问数据
there's plenty more in the document like
文档中还有很多
news at Google's public cloud runs
Google公共云的新闻正在运行
virtual machines in a custom version of
虚拟机在自定义版本中
the kvm hypervisor if you're interested
如果你有兴趣，可以使用kvm管理程序
in seeing the document for yourself you
为您自己查看文档
can access the master at cat 5e TV /
可以访问猫 5e电视/
google dash security I love information
谷歌破折号安全我喜欢信息
like this it just makes me feel far more
像这样，它让我感觉更多
secure alright thanks for watching the
确保对看着好吗谢谢
category 5 TV news room don't forget to
5类电视新闻的房间不要忘记
Like and subscribe for your all your
喜欢和订阅 你的 所有
tech news with a slight Linux bias and
高科技新闻与轻微的Linux偏见和
for more free content be sure to check
为更多免费内容一定要检查
out our website from the category 5 TV
从第 5 类 电视中 删除我们的网站
news room I'm Sasha dramatis
新闻室我是Sasha dramatis
[Music]
[音乐]